# Mary Falcon

ohmfalcon@gmail.com • 707-334-7696 • linkedin.com/in/maryfalcon/ • American Canyon, CA 94503

# Career Summary

I am a recent graduate with BA in Public Health with leadership training experience at the University of California Berkeley. I have proven skills in organization, research, and project management with a background in education, and I am able to provide employers with flexibility, consistency, a solid work ethic, and a commitment to achieving excellence.

#### Education

University of California Berkeley
Bachelor of Arts in Public Health- Cum Laude
Minor in Science and Math Education

Berkeley, CA May 2016

## Experience

#### Rehabilitation Technician at Kindred Healthcare

December 2016-Present

- Maintain and audit patient files and records for the rehab department using Casamba Smart Suite and MS Excel
- Support therapists administratively by printing daily, weekly, monthly progress reports and monitoring accountability
- Assess patient satisfaction by conducting post-rehabilitation surveys
- Data entry for patient records, fax correspondence with patient health offices

### Sports Medicine Intern at Cal Sports Medicine

August 2014- May 2016

- Worked with athletic trainers to help with injury rehabilitation, treatment, and progression for student athletes
- Assisted with re-stocking and organization of medical supplies and maintenance of athletic training room
- Accompanied football and rugby teams to home and away games and administered first-aid as needed

#### Office Assistant at Love and Joy Senior Care Services

June 2011- January 2014

- Created templates for weekly task log, invoice through MS Word and Excel, and helped design brochures and business cards
- Organized files and kept record of patient files through Google Suite

# Collegiate and Community Experience

Academics Co-coordinator for Pilipino Association for Health Careers (PAHC)

August 2015- May 2016

- Maintained and organized resource bank for the organization
- Worked with Kaplan to provide pre-professional resources to members, and worked with other student leaders to plan
  and facilitate general meetings
- Organized and presented semester workshops on research and various academic opportunities

#### Volunteer Research Assistant at Madsen Lab

June 2015- August 2015

- Collected research data by surveying local residents in Berkeley and Oakland regarding opinions and habits about sugary beverages and the effect of the Berkeley soda taxes on consumer opinions
- Data entry into statistical software

#### Volunteer Assistant at Lifelong Medical Care

March 2015- May 2015

- Enrolled patients into Lifelong Patient Portal for direct access to health records
- Worked with support staff at the Lifelong Berkeley Primary Care Center

#### Additional Skills

- Professional proficiency with Microsoft Office Suite and Google Suite
- Experience with Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, and Lightroom
- Basic Knowledge of HTML and CSS
- Bilingual in English and Tagalog (Filipino)

